深い傷を持ってる
そのあった時に
憎しみの裏には
Murderous love
Do you kill your friends? 願い叶うの?
Can you die for someone?
同じなんじゃない
Life is a game is a survival　そうだ
How do you start?
Time and space it’s a crossroad　それで
Where do you go?
求めるは何?
どうしてつづくの?
We don’t know 世界の始まり
We are the time leapers
Nothing’s gonna change with you in the world
すべてが定められてた
Oh we are travelling 未来と過去の狭間
Break out！
痛みを呼び出して
And we will be born again
I wanna see
The stars with you
奇跡を超えて
It’s not a DEAD END
寂しさをもってる
操られた SOUL
憎しみを裏返して
Plundering love
The future　が過ぎ
振り返るは何故?
The past　この先
YES! THEY ARE IN THE SAME TIME
Death is a frame　螺旋のよう、回る！
How do you think?
God and Evil　の終わらない戦い
How do you know?
思うのは何? 手が繋げない
こう言った　”どこへ行く?”
I can’t believe
共に歩こう
Nothing’s gonna change with you in the world
すべてがうまくいくはず
Oh we are wandering　光と闇の中
Break down!
真実を全部変える
And we will create a fact
I wanna feel
The reality
疑いたくても
I love you, 'cause you're always by my side
Death or alive
Back to you
Go!
Can’t you read?
Can’t you see
Go!
My words　幻想的な VISION
Freeze!
Save my life
何故いるの I’m such a liar
Go!
Bad choice!
Bad sign!
Go!
滅びの証のよう
I don’t stop your desire
Cause I can’t forget you
Nothing’s gonna change with you in the world
すべてが定められてた
Oh we are travelling 未来と過去の狭間
Break out!
痛みを呼び出して
And we will be born again
I wanna see
The stars with you
奇跡を超えて
It’s not a DEAD END